var data = [
    {
        id:1,
        question:"Which Indian state has launched the first integrated Air ambulance service of South India?",
        options:["Kerala","Karnataka","Tamil Nadu"," Andhra Pradesh"],
        ans:"Karnataka"
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:"The United Nations World Food Programme (WFP) has partnered with which Indian state to set up supplementary nutrition production units?",
        options:["Bihar","Uttar Pradesh","Uttarakhand","Jharkhand"],
        ans:"Uttar Pradesh"
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question:"Which Ministry has released guidelines to states regarding welfare of migrant workers?",
        options:["Ministry of Home Affairs","Ministry of Social Justice","Ministry of Labour and Employment","Ministry of Finance"],
        ans:"Ministry of Labour and Employment"
    },
    {
        id:4,
        question:"Prime Minister of India has inaugurated three petroleum projects recently, located in which state?",
        options:["Uttar Pradesh","Madhya Pradesh","Bihar","Odisha"],
        ans:"Bihar"
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question:"The DPIIT has extended the date of implementation of Toys (Quality Control) Order till which date?",
        options:["November 30, 2020","January 1, 2021","March 31, 2021","September 30, 2021"],
        ans:"January 1, 2021"
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question:"The Supreme Court has called for setting up of a 5-member panel of distinguished citizens to set standards for which segment?",
        options:["Print Media","Electronic Media","Education","Health"],
        ans:"Electronic Media"
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:"Which institution has directed all Private and Government schools in Delhi to provide gadgets and internet package to poor students?",
        options:["National Human Rights Commission","High Court of Delhi","Supreme Court of India","Central Board of Secondary Education"],
        ans:"High Court of Delhi"
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:"Which state has decided to give 30 % of the new Public Distribution System (PDS) shops to women?",
        options:["Kerala","Uttar Pradesh","Rajasthan","West Bengal"],
        ans:"Rajasthan"
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:"India has provided around 3000 vials of Remdisvir to which country?",
        options:[" Sri Lanka","Myanmar","Thailand","Nepal"],
        ans:"Myanmar"
    },
    {
        id:10,
        question:"What is the name of the mobile application launched by Leather Sector Skill Council (LSSC)?",
        options:["SKILL INDIA","LEATHER INDIA","SCALE INDIA","SCALE SKILL"],
        ans:"SCALE INDIA"
    }
]

export default data